Hey, Jim, Stanley's back
from the hospital today.
Can you sign his card?
Oh, great.
"Glad they didn't mix up your
tonsillectomy with a mustachectomy."
That's not good.
Oh, because your jokes
are all hilarious.
It's nice.
It's funny.
It mentions his
tonsillectomy and makes
a funny little joke
about his mustache.
Stanley doesn't
have a mustache.
Yeah, he does.
Pam, hit the brakes. Stanley
does not have a mustache.
I misspoke, I'm not sure. I think he has one...
I think he has a mustache.
Okay, Phyllis sits
across from him every day.
Phyllis, does he
have a mustache or not?
Oh, I don't know.
Now I think he doesn't.
Phyllis,
what are you talking...
The whole card
depends on this.
Okay, the man's
worked here for 25 years.
How can none of us
picture his face?
Because we come
here to do our jobs.
We don't stick our noses
in other people's business.
Okay. Which one of these
looks more right?
Neither of those
looks like any person
that has ever
existed or been dreamt of
in the history
of human insanity.
That said,
the one on the left.
Guys, that's the elevator.
What if it's him?
Okay, quick,
who says "mustache"?
Yep.
Who says "no mustache"?
Ah!
Hey!
He does have one.
Yes!
Welcome back, Stanley.
"Good morning, Robert,"
says no one
because our receptionist
is in Florida.
Pam!
Oh!
Is this a video conference you're having
with "Drake featuring Swizz Beatz"?
Um, no, I was just
having a cup of coffee
kind of warming up
for the day.
People, you should come
to work already warm.
9:00 to 10:00 a.m. is the most productive
potential that human beings...
Sorry! Sorry,
everyone, I'm late,
but you are all here, so no harm
done at all by my lateness.
Nellie, really, 9:50.
Oh, here's
what happened.
7:46, my alarm clock goes off,
I hear it, whack the snooze.
Nine minutes. Buzz,
off it goes again, whack.
Seven more times I did that.
Buzz, whack, buzz, whack.
By the time I got up,
it was 10 minutes ago.
No will power.
That is my curse.
I've never believed will power
was very important in a woman.
I don't think you would
have shown up to work
nearly an hour late
for no reason.
Oh, I assure you
I would have done.
I did. And I'll keep doing it.
No, no, there's something going
on, some stress in your life.
Well, yes, there is the whole
moving to Scranton nonsense.
Thirty boxes arrived yesterday from
England and two trunks from Florida.
Then, I have to
move into my apartment
in this dreadful,
God knows where it is,
backwater,
suburb of a suburb,
and I mean, no
offense, but are there
a lot of Irish people
living around here?
- Yes.
- Oh!
I hate that.
No offense.
None taken.
Actually, Nellie, this monologue
you're delivering is very offensive.
Ooh! Ay caramba! The natives
are getting restless.
Who's a native?
Excuse me, the tone here
is getting quite hostile.
I would appreciate it if
you would keep that stuff
on the basketball court.
What does that mean?
Okay, okay.
If you'd let me finish.
Or the squash court or
the supreme court. Hmm?
Nellie?
Yes, Robert.
You're clearly under a lot
of stress with the moving
and the work situation
you've found yourself in.
Yeah.
Let's help her out,
shall we?
Go above and beyond today
to show her some of that
warm Scranton hospitality.
Jim, Dwight, take the day.
Help Nellie move those
boxes into her new place.
Why Jim?
What?
The rest of you, let's throw a
party at the end of the day
to welcome the newest member
of our little community.
I'm sorry, we're throwing
a party for someone
because they're
being horrible?
I'm sorry.
We're taking work time
to move someone's personal
belongings into their new apartment.
I'm still not sure why
this woman is even here!
Why is she here?
Two crazy kids
on the journey of life
Going to Pennsylvania
On the road with
my new girlfriend.
But first, a small pit stop to break
up with my current girlfriend,
who is at her parents' cabin
in southern Pennsylvania.
Oh, that must be nice.
Mmm-hmm.
It's a beautiful place. Great
place to let her down easy.
Oh, no, no, I meant that must
be nice to have parents.
Oh. Hmm.
Time to have a little kiss
No.
Mmm. Sorry, right.
No kisses until the
breakup is official. Yes.
I believe in that.
Yes, so do I.
I think that's important. That is important.
Bummer, but important.
Important.
Mmm-hmm.
I can't believe he's making
us throw a party for her.
I know. Right?
She's always late,
she's always rude.
It kind of makes me want to
throw a really bad party.
Yeah.
On purpose.
Phyllis.
We should do it right
here in the break room.
Ooh!
Order carrot cake.
And Jessica,
just so you know,
this is way more about my love for
Erin than anything wrong with you.
Well, Andy, I'm upset, but you did
this in the best way possible,
and I knew you as a lover and
I'll remember you as a gentleman.
Okay. That was one
minute and 10 seconds.
Consider it nailed.
I think we
should try it again.
This time,
worst case scenario.
Okay, here we go. Jessica, I'm really sorry.
I just need you to know...
What?
I just need
you to know...
What? I didn't
sleep well last night.
Ow!
Nellie, that reminds me, do you
want this chair in the bedroom?
'Cause I don't think it's going
to fit through the door.
Don't listen to Jim. Have you
ever seen him play Tetris?
"Oh, I think I'll just
use this line horizontally.
"Oh, I have no idea
what a gift this line is."
That was one time.
I will get the chair in. Watch the
great "Schrut-ini" work his magic.
Oh, no, really? Magic, no,
no, no, let's not go there.
No, nothing is more
repellent than magicians.
Bunch of grown men,
waving wands,
pulling bunnies
out of body crevices.
Magicians are repulsive.
Next topic.
Excuse me, one second.
- Hi.
- Hey, what's up?
Oh, nothing, just hauling
some cube with Dwight.
Hauling cube!
That's moving boxes.
We just came up with the term
to make it sound cooler.
So, we're planning
this party for Nellie,
and we're going to
make it really bad.
It sounds like
every other party.
No, we're going to
make it like a prank,
like order bad food, give her
this passive-aggressive card.
Oh, hire a magician.
What?
Trust me.
Okay.
Wow, there's a lot of cars here.
This is just weird.
Andy. Hi, what are
you doing here?
Hey, Lauren,
look at you.
I know, look at me.
I'm just on my way back
from this business trip,
thought I'd stop
and say hi to Jessica.
Aw!
Why is Erin with me?
That's a great question.
She is my co-worker and she needed a
ride, because she totaled her car.
Oh, God.
So I'm Erin.
Yeah, this is Erin.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Well, Jess went out for a run,
but she'll be back soon.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, ladies,
Andy's here.
Okay, Andy, that is
a bachelorette party.
This is Jessica's friends, and they've
been drinking during the daytime.
Should we go?
Yeah.
You know, we had such a quick
window to make this work.
I think we should
probably just...
Oh, Jess, look who stopped
by after his business trip.
Andy, hey.
I wonder if king-sized sheets are
called presidential-sized in England.
I really should have
a "Tweeter" account.
Yes, you should.
Ooh!
I have to see
these shoes.
I doubt that they're...
Oh.
Who is this guy?
There's the two of them
taking a hike.
I'm guessing he's
some kind of friend.
Boyfriend.
Here's the two of them
kissing at a beach
and kissing at
the Eiffel Tower.
I'm guessing he's some kind
of close, romantic friend.
Like a boyfriend?
You read my mind.
Yeah.
Whoa. Here's one with
his face whited out.
Hmm.
Maybe someone threw
a pie in his face.
New theory, he's a hated
Italian politician.
Better theory,
this is her ex-boyfriend,
and they went through some
kind of painful breakup.
- Oh.
- Nellie,
so sorry,
we were just...
I see you've
discovered Benjamin.
That's what I call my box
full of photos of Henry.
Why not call...
Shh.
God, we owned
this flat together.
Then one morning, just
like that, he was gone.
He ran off with a waitress
at our favorite restaurant.
That's awful.
What kind of restaurant?
Dwight.
I couldn't afford the flat myself.
So I sold it at a loss.
Ah, but what's 10 years
of bliss down the drain
compared with the thrill of starting
over with nothing and no one?
I'm so sorry. These must
be very painful memories.
If it would
help you to forget,
I could hit you in the brain
stem with this candlestick.
Thank you. No.
Look, Jim, Dwight, please,
don't tell anyone about this.
No, no, of course.
Just one quick question,
was this Halloween or...
God, no.
That's the most embarrassing
thing of all of this.
What kind of fool gets her heart
broken by a bloody stage magician?
You know what, Pam? I was thinking
maybe we should change course here.
Let's give up on
all this mean stuff.
What? No. No. I just
had this brilliant idea.
Everyone loved it.
You don't have
a copyright on pranks.
I might be better
at this than you.
No, that's not... Jim,
could you give us a hand?
Absolutely. Yeah.
Call it off, Pam.
Call it off, okay?
It's way more complicated
than you think.
Cancel the magician.
Trust me.
Oh, okay.
Okay, I will.
That's a great idea.
Yeah. Okay.
- Pam, we have a great idea.
- Listen to this.
We're going to have the
fluorescent lights flickering.
It's going to
make everyone sick.
Or what if...
Okay.
...we discuss the idea of doing
the party totally normal.
Like, not mean.
Just a regular party.
Not mean.
I knew she'd crack. I wanted
to leave you out, you know.
We're in far too deep. We can't
change course at this point.
What are you talking about?
Of course we can.
What I mean to say is
we don't want to.
Toots, we're not stopping this
train, so get off the tracks.
Suck it!
Andy.
It'll be fine. Just act natural.
Do you want a gummy penis?
No. I'll just have
some gummy bears.
These are delicious.
But they're penises.
And we come to Matthew,
the guy who was
with his old girlfriend
basically the whole time
we were together.
Oh, no.
Eww! That seems gross
at first blush, right?
But relationships are always
more complicated than you think.
I mean, we don't know Matthew's
history with this other woman.
Maybe she saved his life.
I don't know.
I just...
I don't think we should
rush to judgment
about Matthew.
Maybe we don't
pop that one.
No. Pop it.
Pop it!
LAUREN; Pop it!
HEY
Sorry. It's kind of a mad house.
Oh, Megan.
You are one of the good
ones, Nard Dog. Aw!
No, really.
Where's my Andy?
He's out there.
Are you going to
sing for us?
Well, you guys are doing a pretty good
job with the scary yelling, so...
That's not like you. That's not like you.
Come on, sing! Sing!
By yon bonnie banks
and by yon bonnie braes
Okay, they're almost here.
What?
Come on! If you guys
are going to be mean,
can't you at least
be subtle?
Oh, in the warehouse,
we'd use code names
for people we
wanted to talk about.
Andy was "Jelly Roll." Mike
was "Dennis the Menace."
Ryan was "Douche Bag."
Hey, that's not a code name.
That's just an insult.
Plus, everyone would know
who you meant. Yeah.
No, that's a great idea.
Yes, let's have a code name.
How about "Mondays"? I hate Mondays.
Mondays are the worst.
Nobody's named Monday.
Hey, how about we go with "Pam"?
Simple, easy to remember.
Because there's someone
already here named Pam.
Shh. Here she comes.
Hey.
Welcome to your party.
Everybody, get comfy now. This first
song's over a half-hour long.
Best gig ever. They asked
me to play only originals.
I said, "Have you heard my originals?
They're terrible."
They said, "Even better." I said, "I get it.
It's an ironic party for Nellie."
Maybe we should just go.
No, I got to do this.
Hey, Jessica,
can I talk to you?
Uh, yeah, sure,
what's up?
Maybe we could
talk in private.
Yeah, what is it?
Well, first,
let me just say that
I hope when I'm done with
the sort of ugly bits,
that we can
stay friends.
You're breaking up
with me?
Uh...
No. No.
You always do this.
You twist my words around.
Part of me thinks we should
just end this right now.
Oh, my God. Are you
leaving me for Erin?
You said she wasn't relationship
material, and she wasn't as good as me.
But it's her, isn't it?
Whoa.
That... No.
Okay, you want honesty?
Super honesty time.
I'm gay.
What?
I am gay and
I prefer men.
I knew it!
You did not, Kenny.
You invited me to
go shopping with you.
I like hanging outwith you.
You're a cool guy.
Which proves my point
that I'm gay.
Andy, you're not gay.
I mean, we were together and
you seemed pretty excitable.
Well, I was faking it.
I had to fake it every time.
I had to imagine that I was in
a steam room with John Stamos.
I can't say it
doesn't make sense.
Well, I mean, I was
good at hiding it...
It's fine, Andy.
I didn't think we were going
to get married or anything.
I just...
I'm just upset for now.
Understandable, and I'm really sorry.
I really am.
So, we should probably go.
This humble
but sincere effort is
all for our valued new colleague.
Excellent.
To Nellie Bertram,
you are a most welcome
and friendly presence
at our company.
Cheers.
Why, thank you.
Pam, on the other hand,
is a most unwelcome,
entitled and unfriendly
presence in our company.
Cheers.
Nellie is terrific,
but to be honest,
every day, I imagine how
happy I'd be if Pam died.
Oh, well, I feel that as
someone who knows Pam,
only a little bit, enough, a good
amount, not the most, though,
I would say that
she is misunderstood,
and that maybe there's
some stuff in her past
that you guys
don't know about
that's a little
messed up and probably
makes her such a
torture to work with.
We hate Pam! We hate Pam!
So we've established...
No.
...that you guys hate Pam.
Do you ever wish she
would just disappear?
Oh!
That was a really
rough scene.
Right? Rough scene.
Yeah.
At least we can kiss now.
Oh, yeah.
You know, that stuff that I said
about you to her, that's just...
I had to say it.
You know, I was dating
her at the time.
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
Ugh.
I feel really tired.
Yeah.
Probably from
seeing that turkey.
Oh, yeah.
When we drove by the farm.
Always does that.
Are you Nellie? I think
you're my volunteer.
Come on
over here, huh?
No, I'll do it.
I will volunteer.
No, Nellie should.
No, I'll do it.
Oh, big guy, huh? How's the air up there?
Watch out for birds.
All right, let's do
some card magic.
Now, what I want
you to do is,
I want you to pick a card
just by looking at it.
Do not say what it is.
It's the four of hearts.
Oh, no, it's...
Looks like we got a guy from
another country here, huh?
No hablo el cardo, señior?
All right, the card is picked. Now,
sir, will you please shuffle the deck?
You didn't just do that
on purpose, did you?
Why is Jim treating
the magician poorly?
Little known fact about me,
before I was a magician,
I used to work
at a rope factory.
Not true because
that's not a real place.
But I never could seem to
figure out those knots.
That's not a real knot. When
you pull on it, it disappears.
What the hell?
All right! Where's Phyllis?
Who's Phyllis?
Look, this is really uncool, okay?
I put on a clean show here...
Okay, scram, wizard!
What?
You heard me!
Wow. Nellie, I'm sorry.
If I'd known
Jim and Pam
would use this party
as an excuse to
abuse a magician...
Well, I thought
it was quite fun.
In fact, I think they're brilliant
employees in their own way.
Don't you see
what I see?
Interesting, yes.
No, yes, I see that.
Great work, team.
Great party.
You think this
is a great party?
This cake has vegetables in
it, like a salad bar, Robert.
How do I get this
taste out of my mouth?
What? Why are we...
I just got to do
one thing.
Oh, hello.
Hey, everybody,
look who's here.
What are you doing here?
Hi. Super duper honesty
time, I'm not gay.
In fact, I'm so not gay that
I'm in love with a girl.
Her name is Erin Hannon,
and she is right there.
She's sweet,
funny and beautiful
and total
relationship material.
Why the hell did
you come back here?
Go away.
Get lost.
Get out!
Okay.
You're done! Get out!
Bye, guys. Go. Go.
You ruined my party.
Who does that?
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, run away.
Run away!
You're disgusting!
I can't believe
you're not gay!
Yeah,
get out of here.
Don't come back!
Uh-oh.
You don't even
know how to drive!
Loser! Nice car!
Hey, Hank.
Yes, ma'am.
I thought I was very specific about
you not letting up a magician.
Yes, ma'am,
I got my eyes open.
Well, turns out he
actually made it up there.
What? That ain't right.
Yeah, he came and went.
Wait a minute, you said
it was a magician, right?
You don't think he could have used...
It couldn't have been...
Let's just go.
Good night, Hank.